A Guide to the Trilateral Commission (North America) records FA420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Publications, 1973-2000; 3; 14.02 Cubic Feet 30 letter document boxes and 2 record storage boxes
  - Annual Reports
    - Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 239, Folder 2605)
    - Annual Report, 1987-1988, 1988-1989 (Box 239, Folder 2606)
    - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 239, Folder 2607)
    - Annual Report - Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 239, Folder 2608)
  - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Publication Distribution Files
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Micropage/Capital City (Box 239A, Folder 3841)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Brookings, 1993-1994 (Box 239A, Folder 3842)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - T47, 6 folders (Box 239A, Folder 3843)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - China Report, 1994; 4 folders (Box 239A, Folder 3844)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up and Mailed, 1994 October-December (Box 239A, Folder 3845)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up and Mailed, 1994 April-June (Box 239A, Folder 3846)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up and Mailed, 1994 January-March (Box 239A, Folder 3847)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub-Dead Invoices (Box 239A, Folder 3848)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Old Versions of Forms (Box 239A, Folder 3849)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Subscribers Prior to Reconstruction (Box 239A, Folder 3850)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Old Subsriber Lists (Box 239A, Folder 3851)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Subscriber List, 19941993-March November (Box 239A, Folder 3852)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Subscriber List, 1994 April-May (Box 239A, Folder 3853)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Old Subscriber List, Pre-April 30, 1995 (Box 239A, Folder 3854)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Subscribers as of February 1, 1993 (Box 239A, Folder 3855)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Book Orders Shipped, 1993 (Box 239A, Folder 3856)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Brookings Flier Mailing, 1993 December 3 (Box 239A, Folder 3857)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution (Box 239A, Folder 3858)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - In House Mailing Lists, 1993 (Box 239A, Folder 3859)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Capital City Mailing, 1993 August (Box 239A, Folder 3860)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Migration/Peacekeeping/Regionalism Subscriber Mailings, 1993 (Box 239A, Folder 3861)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Mailing, 1993 February (Box 239A, Folder 3862)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Working Group Papers and Complimentary Respondents and Target Mailing (Box 239A, Folder 3863)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Subscribers, 1994 (Box 239A, Folder 3864)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Book Orders Shipped, 1992 (Box 239A, Folder 3865)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Target Mailing, 1992 (Box 239A, Folder 3866)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Complimentary Query, 1992 (Box 239A, Folder 3867)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Subscriber Mailing, 1992 October 23 (Box 239A, Folder 3868)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Environment, 1991 (Box 239A, Folder 3869)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Subscriber and PS Lists, 1995 November 29 (Box 239B, Folder 3870)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - T48, 1995 October (Box 239B, Folder 3871)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - T48 - Comp and Target, 1995 (Box 239B, Folder 3872)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Target - Russia Flier, 1995 August 16 (Box 239B, Folder 3873)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up Mailed, 1995 October (Box 239B, Folder 3874)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up Mailed, 1995 July-September (Box 239B, Folder 3875)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - T48 Mailings, 1995 August (Box 239B, Folder 3876)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Russia Report, 5 folders (Box 239B, Folder 3877)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - T49, 5 folders (Box 239B, Folder 3878)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Democracy Reports - Mailings to Subscribers (Box 239B, Folder 3879)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Mailings, 1995 (Box 239B, Folder 3880)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Energy Report, 1996 September (Box 239B, Folder 3881)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Energy Report (Box 239B, Folder 3882)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Globalization Report - Mailings, 1996 December (Box 239B, Folder 3883)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Globalization Report, 3 folders (Box 239B, Folder 3884)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up and Mailed, 1996 January-March (Box 239B, Folder 3885)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up and Mailed, 1996 April-June (Box 239B, Folder 3886)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up and Mailed, 1996 July-September (Box 239B, Folder 3887)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up and Mailed, 1996 October-December (Box 239B, Folder 3888)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Subscribers, 1995 (Box 239B, Folder 3889)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up and Mailed, 1995 April-June (Box 239B, Folder 3890)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up and Mailed, 1995 February (Box 239B, Folder 3891)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Sub/SO Paid Up and Mailed, 1995 January (Box 239B, Folder 3892)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Renewal Notices Sent, 1995 (Box 239B, Folder 3893)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Publications Distribution - Mailing Memos, 1992-1997 (Box 239B, Folder 3894)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1996 (Box 239B, Folder 3895)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1995 (Box 239B, Folder 3896)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Perry Financials (Box 239B, Folder 3897)
    - Rohesia Hamilton Metcalfe Files - Perry Fundraising (Box 239B, Folder 3898)
- Membership, 1978-1980s; 4; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
  When the Trilateral Commission was initially established, the intention had been to have an equal number of members from each of the three regions. Initial membership consisted of approximately 190 members. 1. North America (United States and Canada); 2. Europe (Belgium, Denmark, France, Ireland, Italy, Luxembourg, Netherlands, Norway, U.K., West Germany); 3. Japan.
  Around 1980, membership ceilings were imposed for the three regions. These ceilings have been periodically raised as new countries are added.
  Membership ceilings as of 2011 are: North America – 120 (87 US, 20 Canada, 13 Mexico). Europe – 160 (20 members each for Germany, France, Italy, U.K.)(14 Spain), (The remaining national quotas range from 4 to 9). Pacific Asian – 100+ In 2000, the Japanese group of 85 members was expanded and restructured. The new configuration is 57 Japan, 15 Korea, 8 Australia & New Zealand, 16 from 5 ASEAN Countries (Indonesia, Malaysia, Philippines, Singapore and Thailand). By 2008, the Pacific Asian group was comprised of more than 100 members. Individuals from Taiwan, Hong Kong and the People's Republic of China have also participated.
  Membership is by invitation. For the North American group, invitations are decided upon by the Executive Committee, on the basis of recommendations by members and staff. Members are generally corporate, political, educational and non-profit leaders including prominent businessmen, journalists, academicians, non-profit executives, union and labor leaders and politicians. New members are chosen on a national basis. Membership procedures differ slightly depending on the national region. Members who accept positions in the executive branch of their government must forfeit their Commission membership.
  The Trilateral Commission archives does not contain much documentation of the Commission's membership. Most North American membership files remain at the North American Office in Washington, D.C. Membership files for other regions are at their respective offices.
  - Membership - Japanese, 1975-1986 (Box 240, Folder 2609)
  - Membership - European, 1977-1986 (Box 240, Folder 2610)
  - Member Participation, 1975-1986 (Box 240, Folder 2611)
  - U.S. Membership Matters, 1975-1986 (Box 240, Folder 2612)
  - Membership, 1973-1995 (Box 240, Folder 2613)
  - Membership, 1996-2000 (Box 240, Folder 2613A)
  - Japanese Commissioners, 1973-1990 (Box 240, Folder 2614)
  - Early European Membership, 1972-1979 (Box 240, Folder 2615)
  - European Membership Matters, 1979-1991 (Box 241, Folder 2616)
  - European Membership Matters, 1996-1998 (Box 241, Folder 2616A)
  - European Membership Matters, 1973-1981 (Box 241, Folder 2617)
  - Membership, 1984 (Box 241, Folder 2618)
  - Printed Membership Lists, Corporate Sponsors (and Task Force Brochure), 19851978-1981 (Box 241, Folder 2619)
  - TC Membership Breakdown by Location and Occupation, 1981-1984 (Box 241, Folder 2620)
  - Membership, 1979-1980 (Box 241, Folder 2621)
  - Membership, Post-March 1985, 1985-1986 (Box 241, Folder 2622)
- Officer's Files, 1974-1998; 5; 38.43 Cubic Feet 69 letter document boxes, 12 legal document boxes, and 5 record storage boxes.
  Leadership of the Trilateral Commission is composed of: 1. Regional Chairman (one from each of the three regions); 2. Deputy Chairman; 3. Directors; 4. Executive Committee (36 other members, exact total of membership fluctuates).
  North American Chairmen: Gerard C. Smith, 1973-1977 (from establishment in 1973-mid 1977); David Rockefeller, 1977-1991 (also Founder and Honorary North American chairman); Paul A. Volcker, 1991-2001 (also Honorary North American Chairman); Thomas S. Foley, 2001-2008; Joseph S. Nye, Jr., 2009-.
  European Chairmen: Max Kohnstamm, 1973-1976; Georges Berthoin, 1976-1992 (also Honorary European Chairman); Otto Graf Lambsdorff, 1992-2001 (also Honorary European Chairman); Peter Sutherland, 2001-2010 (also Honary European Chairman); Mario Monti, 2010-.
  Japanese Chairmen: Takeshi Watanabe, 1973-1985; Isamu Yamashita, 1985-1992; Akio Morita, 1992-1993; Kiichi Miyazawa, Acting Chairmen, 1993-1997; Yotaro Kobayashi, Current (Pacific Asian Chairman).
  Records are primarily arranged alphabetically, by the last name of the officer. 1. Zbigniew Brzezinski - Director of the Trilateral Commission from its inception in 1973 through mid-1976. In 1975-1976 Brzezinski served part-time and Christopher Makins was Deputy Director. Archival holdings include chronological files, January 1975-June 1976.
  2. George S. Franklin - North American Secretary from mid 1973 through 1976. Franklin served as the Commission's Coordinator from early 1977 through mid- 1982. Archival holdings are primarily chronological files, August 1974-1994 and a selection of alphabetical files.
  3. Charles B. Heck - Joined the Commission staff in 1974 as assistant to the Director (Zbigniew Brzezinski). In 1976 Heck became Deputy North American Secretary, then North American Secretary (1977-1981) and North American Director (1982-2001). Charles Heck was also editor of the Task Force reports from 1974-1991. Archival holdings are primarily meeting records and chronological files 1974-1998. The collection also holds a limited selection of office records created by assistants to Charles Heck including: Catherine Katin (Assistant to Charles Heck, 1977-1979); Daniel Newman (Assistant to Charles Heck, 1981-1984); and Erna Prickett Adelson (Assistant to Charles Heck, 1979-1981).
  4. Christopher Makins – Trilateral Commission Deputy Director, August 1975-June 1976. Makins began his career in the British diplomatic service with posts in London, Paris, Washington, D.C. and others. He then shifted his focus to U.S/European relations with appointments in organizations including, but not limited to: the Atlantic Council of the United States, the Aspen Institute, the German Marshall Fund and the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace. Makins served the Trilateral Commission in a variety of capacities, most notably as Deputy Director. Archival holdings include chronological files from August 1975-June 1976.
  5. David Rockefeller – Founder and North American Chairman, 1977-1991. David Rockefeller served as Chairman and Chief Executive Officer of Chase Manhattan Bank (now J.P. Morgan Chase Bank), from 1969-1980. Rockefeller relinquished his chairmanship of Chase Manhattan Bank in 1981. Archival holdings include chronological files, 1985-1998, and a selection of speeches, 1977-1980.
  6. Gerard C. Smith – Before becoming Trilateral Commission North American Chairman in 1973, Smith served as Director of the Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, and Chief United States negotiator of the Strategic Arms Limitation (SALT I) talks, which led to the Antiballistic Missile (ABM) Treaty of 1972. In mid-1977, he relinquished his Commission chairmanship to become Ambassador for Non-Proliferation Issues in the Carter administration. Smith had his office in Washington D.C. while the Trilateral Commission Director and North American staff were in New York. The Smith files represented in the collection were shipped to New York after Smith's chairmanship had concluded.
  7. Paul A.Volcker – North American Chairman, 1991-2001. Paul Volcker served as Chairman of the Board of Governors of the Federal Reserve System from August 1979-August 1987. Archival holdings are chronological files, 1991-1998.
  Documentation of the correspondence and activities of the Commission's officers is prevalent throughout the Trilateral Commission archives. Users of Series 5 are advised to also consider Series 6 Office Files, particularly the Early Office files.
  Existence and Location of Copies
  Microfilm copies of portions of the Zbigniew Brzezinski Files (Box 241A), Gerard C. Smith Files (Box 308B-P), and Trilateral Commission Early Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 310A-B) are available at the Jimmy Carter Library, Atlanta, GA.
  - Zbigniew Brzezinski, 5.1
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 January (Box 241A, Folder 4117)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 February (Box 241A, Folder 4118)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 March (Box 241A, Folder 4119)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 April (Box 241A, Folder 4120)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 May (Box 241A, Folder 4121)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 June (Box 241A, Folder 4122)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 July (Box 241A, Folder 4123)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 August (Box 241A, Folder 4124)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 September (Box 241A, Folder 4125)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 October (Box 241A, Folder 4126)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 November (Box 241A, Folder 4127)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1975 December (Box 241A, Folder 4128)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1976 January (Box 241A, Folder 4129)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1976 February (Box 241A, Folder 4130)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1976 March (Box 241A, Folder 4131)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1976 April (Box 241A, Folder 4132)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1976 May (Box 241A, Folder 4133)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski Chronological Files, 1976 June (Box 241A, Folder 4134)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 241A, Folder 4135)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski - Travel (Box 241A, Folder 4136)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski - Expense Reports (Box 241A, Folder 4137)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski - Invitations (Box 241A, Folder 4138)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski - Mailing Lists and Salutations (Box 241A, Folder 4139)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski - Mid Atlantic Clubs (Box 241A, Folder 4140)
    - Zbigniew Brzezinski - Correspondence with Commissioners (Box 241A, Folder 4141)
  - George S. Franklin, 5.2
    - George Franklin Chronological Files
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1974 July (Box 242, Folder 2623)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1974 August (Box 242, Folder 2623A)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1974 September (Box 242, Folder 2624)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1974 October (Box 242, Folder 2625)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1974 November (Box 242, Folder 2626)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1974 December (Box 242, Folder 2627)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1975 January-March (Box 243, Folder 2628)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1975 April-June (Box 243, Folder 2629)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1975 July (Box 244, Folder 2630)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1975 August (Box 244, Folder 2631)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1975 September (Box 244, Folder 2632)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1975 October (Box 244, Folder 2633)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1975 November (Box 244, Folder 2634)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1975 December (Box 244, Folder 2635)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1976 January (Box 244, Folder 2636)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1976 February (Box 245, Folder 2637)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1976 March (Box 245, Folder 2638)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1976 April (Box 245, Folder 2639)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1976 May-July (Box 245, Folder 2640)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1976 August-September (Box 246, Folder 2641)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1976 October (Box 246, Folder 2641A)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1976 November (Box 246, Folder 2642)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1976 December (Box 247, Folder 2643)
      - George Franklin Correspondence with Commissioner and Staff, 1976 (Box 247, Folder 2644)
      - George Franklin Correspondence - Impact, 1976 (Box 247, Folder 2645)
      - George Franklin Italian Trip Bills, 1976 (Box 247, Folder 2646)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 January (Box 248, Folder 2647)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 February (Box 248, Folder 2648)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 March (Box 248, Folder 2649)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 April (Box 248, Folder 2650)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 May (Box 249, Folder 2651)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 June (Box 249, Folder 2652)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 July (Box 249, Folder 2653)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 August (Box 249, Folder 2654)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 September (Box 249, Folder 2655)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 October (Box 250, Folder 2656)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 November (Box 250, Folder 2657)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1977 December (Box 250, Folder 2658)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 January (Box 251, Folder 2659)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 February (Box 251, Folder 2660)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 March (Box 251, Folder 2661)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 April (Box 251, Folder 2662)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 May (Box 252, Folder 2663)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 June (Box 252, Folder 2664)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 July (Box 252, Folder 2665)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 August (Box 252, Folder 2666)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 September (Box 252, Folder 2667)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 October (Box 253, Folder 2668)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 November (Box 253, Folder 2669)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1978 December (Box 253, Folder 2670)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 January (Box 254, Folder 2671)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979-1981 (Box 254, Folder 2671A)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 February (Box 254, Folder 2672)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 March (Box 254, Folder 2673)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 April (Box 255, Folder 2674)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 May (Box 255, Folder 2675)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 June (Box 255, Folder 2676)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 July (Box 255, Folder 2677)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 August (Box 256, Folder 2678)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 September (Box 256, Folder 2679)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 October (Box 256, Folder 2680)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 November (Box 256, Folder 2681)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1979 December (Box 256, Folder 2682)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 January (Box 257, Folder 2683)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 February (Box 257, Folder 2684)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 March (Box 257, Folder 2685)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 April (Box 257, Folder 2686)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 May (Box 257, Folder 2687)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 June (Box 257, Folder 2688)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 July (Box 257, Folder 2689)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 August (Box 257, Folder 2690)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 September (Box 258, Folder 2691)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 October (Box 258, Folder 2692)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 November (Box 258, Folder 2693)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1980 December (Box 258, Folder 2694)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1981 January (Box 258, Folder 2695)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1981 February (Box 258, Folder 2696)
      - George Franklin Chronological Files, 1981 March (Box 258, Folder 2697)